

CONTACT



ishanmwaduge@gmail.com



Phone +94 76 7711 597 +94 70 2012 900



Website imwaduge.me

SOCIAL MEDIA

LinkedIn in linkedin.com/in/imwaduge

Behance

behance.net/imwaduge

Вē

Github github.com/imwaduge

TECHNICAL SKILLS

UI/UX Design

Wireframing | Prototyping

Logo & Brand Identity Design

Digital Marketing

Web Development

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React JS

PHP | MySQL

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Figma | Adobe XD

Adobe Illustrator | Photoshop

Premiere Pro | After Effects

Microsoft Office Package

ISHAN MADUSANKA

UI/UX DESIGNER | UNDERGRADUATE

PROFILE

I am a freelance designer with five years of experience. I have completed more than 250 projects for international clients since 2018. To Expand my knowledge, I am pursuing a Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology (Honours) degree specializing in multimedia technology at the University of Sri Jayawardenepura. I am passionate about using my skills to help organizations overcome challenges and succeed long-term. I am currently looking for career opportunities that will allow me to work together with teams and clients to create user - friendly solutions for the digital world. I enjoy working in an environment that offers growth and learning opportunities.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology Honours

2020 - Present

Faculty of Technology, University of Sri Jayewardenepura

(Undergraduate - BICT Hons)

G.C.E Advanced Level Examination - Technology Stream

2016 - 2018



🔀 St' Anthony's College

Information and Communication Technology - A Engineering Technology - B Science For Technology - B

Z Score - 2.16

District Rank - 11

G.C.E Ordinary Level Examination

2005 - 2015



🖲 G/Saralankara Maha Vidyalaya

Information and Communication Technology - A

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Services

2023 - Present



UI/UX design, Logo & Brand identity design, Packaging design, Website and Web application development, Video production.

UI/UX Designer

2022 - Present



UI/UX design, Front-end development, Logo & Brand identity design, Logo animation.

Brand Designer

2019 - Present



As an experienced graphic designer with 5 years of industry expertise, I have honed my skills in Brand identity design and UI/UX design. I have successfully completed over 250 projects.

SOFT SKILLS

Creative thinking

Team work

Problem-solving

Multi-tasking

INTERESTS

UI/UX Design

Front End Development

Logo Design

Brand Identity Design

Digital Marketing

TEST SCORES

Adobe Illustrator Test - Fiverr

2021 Score: 8/10 (TOP 10%)

Adobe Photoshop Test - Fiverr

2021 Score: 9.5/10 (TOP 10%)

PERSONAL INFORMATION

NAME - Ishan Madusanka Waduge

ADDRESS - Basswatta, Mahawella

Road, Gonapinuwala,

Galle, Sri Lanka

BIRTHDAY - 22.06.1999

GENDER - Male

NIC - 991746927v

LANGUAGES - Sinhala, English

NON-RELATED REFEREES

Dr. Pulasthi Gunawardhana

Senior Lecturer

Department of

 $Information\ and\ Communication\ Technology,$

Faculty o Technology,

University of Sri Jayewardenepura.

Email : pulasthi@sjp.ac.lk Mobile : +94 77 488 6388

Chamila Karunatilake

Lecturer

Department of

 $Information\ and\ Communication\ Technology,$

Faculty of Technology,

University of Sri Jayewardenepura.

Email : chamilakarunatilake@sjp.ac.lk

Mobile: +94 76 460 8026

PROJECTS

J'pura FOSS Community - UI/UX design

I designed the user interface and user experience for the J'pura FOSS.

Plot details system for divisional secretariat - Web development

I designed and developed a CRUD system for the divisional secretariat, creating wireframes, designing the user interface, coding the system, and testing functionality.

GPSI premium car service center - Web development

Designed and developed a website for a car service center.

HireNow - Service selling platform (Group)

UI/UX design and developed web-based "HireNow" Service selling platform using Figma, HTML, CSS, JS, React JS.

Automated plant watering system (Group)

Design mobile application UI for the automated plant watering system.

Ocean Epic - Game designed. (windows, android)

Web based online type racing game design- UI/UX design

CERTIFICATION

English Diploma in British Way English Academy

Graphic Design Course in Future World IPS

Computer Hardware Engineering Course in Nanasa Education Institute

Digital Marketing Course in Google Digital Garage

Front End Development - HTML Course in Great Learning Academy

Front End Development - CSS Course in Great Learning Academy

UI / UX Course in Great Learning Academy

Introduction to Design Thinking Course in Great Learning Academy

Adobe Premiere Pro CC 2023 Course in Udemy

JavaScript | Ultimate Guide Course in Udemy

React Js Courses in Udemy (Ongoing)

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Participated in UI/UX Challenge - Design Code 2022

Participated in several gaming competition

Graphic designer at the J'PURA FOSS Community

Member of the J'PURA Flames

Passed the Dhamma School Final Certificate Examination

Senior Prefect in 2014, 2015

DECLARATION

I certify that the above details and informations are true and accurate to the best of my knowledge.

24.05.2023

Date

